this week we're going to tell you about
这周我们要告诉你
one of the great success stories of
伟大的成功故事之一
mechanism design the victory Clark
机制设计胜利克拉克
groves mechanism and in this video I'm
格罗夫机制，在这个视频中，我是
going to give you a high-level taste of
给你高层次的品味
what this mechanism does and why it's
该机制的作用以及原因
important so what is the Vickery Clark
重要的是什么，维克·克拉克是什么
groves mechanism for essentially it
格罗夫机制实质上
solves a problem that we encounter in
解决了我们遇到的一个问题
mechanism design pretty often where I as
我经常在哪里设计机构
the designer and interested in
设计师感兴趣
implementing an efficient outcome what
实施有效的结果是什么
that means is I've got a set of
那意味着我有一套
self-interested agents each of whom has
每个人都有的利己代理
private information about how much they
关于他们多少的私人信息
value each of the different things that
珍惜每一个不同的事物
could happen in the world and what I'm
可能发生在世界上，我是什么
desiring to do is always to pick the
渴望做的总是选择
thing that maximizes the sum of the ways
使方式总和最大化的事物
that the agents actually feel about
代理商真正感觉到的
these different things which of course
这些不同的东西，当然
is something that I as the designer
是我作为设计师的东西
don't know so what I need is for the
不知道，所以我需要的是
agents to tell me how much they value
代理商告诉我他们有多重视
different things and I want them to pick
不同的东西，我希望他们选择
the thing that maximizes the sum of
最大化总和的东西
their values this would all be fine
他们的价值观，这一切都很好
except that of course the agents could
当然代理商可以
lie to me about how much they value
对我撒谎他们有多重视
different things so what I want to do in
不同的事情，所以我想做什么
a transferable utility setting here is
这里的可转移实用程序设置是
to impose a set of payments that make it
施加一系列的付款
the right thing for the agents to tell
代理商告诉的正确的事情
me the truth so that I can then solve
给我真相，以便我可以解决
the pretty simple problem of maximizing
最大化这个非常简单的问题
the sum of how they feel about the
他们对
different things the trick is to set up
设置技巧的不同之处
these payments in the right way so that
这些付款方式正确，以便
the agents really will want to tell me
代理商真的会想告诉我
the truth
真相
the great success of the VCG mechanism
VCG机制的巨大成功
is that telling the truth for the agents
是为代理商讲真话
is a dominant strategy so it's a really
是一项占主导地位的策略
strong kind of implementation the agents
代理商执行力强
really will want to tell me the truth
真的会想告诉我真相
and they don't even have to think about
他们甚至不必考虑
what the other agents will do it's
其他代理商会做什么
simply the right thing for every agent
对于每个代理商来说都是正确的事情
to tell me the truth about their own
告诉我关于自己的真相
valuation and then if I run the BCG
评估，然后如果我运行BCG
mechanism the payments will be such that
机制的付款将使得
the agents will feel like they've done
代理商会觉得自己已经完成了
the right thing by just telling me the
告诉我正确的事情
truth I'm going to show you a number of
真相，我将向您展示一些
different examples that gives you a
不同的例子给你
sense of what this means in practice and
在实践中理解这意味着什么
why it's exciting let's start with with
为什么令人兴奋，让我们开始
the simplest example where I'm going to
我要去的最简单的例子
allocate a single thing among a set of
在一组中分配一个东西
agents so imagine a government that
特工们想像一个政府
wants to privatize a public utility like
想要私有化像
a power play
权力游戏
now when a government wants to privatize
现在，当一个政府想要私有化时
something it's not usually because it
有些事情通常不是因为
just wants to collect a bunch of money
只想收一大笔钱
but instead it's that the government
而是政府
thinks that this public utility could be
认为该公用事业可能是
more efficiently operated by somebody in
有人更有效地操作
the private sector than by the
私营部门比
government if this is the case the
如果是这样，政府
government typically wants to figure out
政府通常想弄清楚
which among a set of potential buyers
在一组潜在买家中
values the utility the most because
最重视该实用程序，因为
that's the buyer that would then most
那就是当时的买家
efficiently operate the utility
有效地运行该实用程序
afterwards so you could sort of think
之后，您可以考虑一下
the government could go to each of these
政府可以去做每一个
potential buyers and ask them how much
潜在买家并询问他们多少
do you value the power plant and it
您是否重视电厂及其
could then just give the power plant to
然后可以将发电厂交给
the utility that values at the most the
最重视
problem of course is that if it just did
当然，问题在于，如果这样做
this the buyers would lie they would all
买家会撒谎，他们都会
claim very very high values in the hopes
在希望中要求很高的价值
of being the highest and the government
最高和政府
would probably not end up giving the
可能最终不会给
power plant to the right company so
发电厂给合适的公司
instead the government has to sell the
相反，政府必须出售
power plant even if it doesn't care
发电厂，即使它不在乎
about collecting the money the question
关于收钱的问题
then is what rules should it use for
那应该用什么规则
imposing payments on the different
将付款强加给其他人
potential buyers and if we were to use
潜在的买家，如果我们要使用
the VCG mechanism here this would give
这里的VCG机制
us a way of imposing payments on the
向我们收取费用的一种方式
different buyers so that we would ensure
不同的买家，以便我们确保
that each of the buyers would simply
每个购买者只会
tell the government the truth about how
告诉政府真相
much the power plant is worth to them
电厂对他们来说值得
this is a simple example because here
这是一个简单的示例，因为这里
the outcome space is just giving the
结果空间只是给
power plant to each of the potential
发电厂的每一个潜力
buyers and we're just allocating a
买家，我们只是分配一个
single good essentially the the power
单品本质上就是力量
plant here but VCG also works in other
在这里种植，但VCG也可以在其他地方使用
settings that look pretty different from
看起来与
this let me give you an example of that
这让我举一个例子
let's imagine here the the simplest
让我们想象一下最简单的
possible outcome space there are just
可能的结果空间只有
two things that could happen I have a
我可能有两件事
set of businesses on two sides of a
一组业务的两个侧面
river and the two outcomes are that a
河和两个结果是
bridge could be built or could not be
桥梁可以建造还是不能建造
built and what I want to do here is to
内置的，我想在这里做的是
build the bridge if the sum of values
如果价值总和建立桥梁
that the agents have for the bridge
代理商为桥梁准备的
exceeds the cost of it
超过它的成本
construction and not build the bridge
建造而不是建造桥梁
otherwise and again what what I want to
否则，我想要什么
do here is collect information from all
这里要做的是从所有人那里收集信息
the businesses that that has them tell
让他们知道的企业
me how much it's worth to them to have
我对他们来说有多少价值
the bridge be constructed and it may
建造桥梁，它可能
well be that they have a negative value
很有可能它们具有负值
for the bridge being constructed because
对于正在建造的桥梁，因为
maybe they're better off in the world
也许他们在这个世界上更好
where there's no bridge so I want to
没有桥所以我想
look at all of this aggregate
看看所有这些汇总
information and I want them to to figure
信息，我希望他们去思考
out payments where I might compensate
我可以补偿的付款
some businesses that are hurt by the
一些受到
construction of the bridge
桥梁的建设
I might charge some businesses that are
我可能会收费一些
benefited by the cost of the bridge and
受益于桥梁的成本和
eventually collect enough money that I
最终收集到足够的钱，我
can actually pay the construction
可以实际支付建设费用
workers who of course have a negative
当然有负面的工人
value for the bridge being constructed
正在建造的桥梁的价值
because they have to do work and overall
因为他们必须做工作和整体
decide whether the bridge in fact should
决定实际上是否应该桥梁
be built or not so again the VCG
是否再次建造
mechanism would just do the right thing
机制只会做正确的事
here would come up with payments that
这里会拿出付款
work out in the right way as we'll see
以正确的方式进行锻炼，我们将看到
when we do this example a bit more
当我们做这个例子多一点
formally later here's a third example
正式之后，这是第三个例子
which is again pretty different from the
再次与
first two it's a little bit more like
前两个有点像
the bridge example I need to make kind
我需要亲切的桥梁例子
of a social choice here rather than
在这里是一种社会选择，而不是
allocating one thing among different
在不同事物之间分配一件事
people here the problem is scheduling
人们在这里问题是日程安排
meetings so imagine that you're in a
开会，想象一下您正在
problem which I really face in my life
我一生中真正面对的问题
all the time where it's necessary to
一直在需要
schedule meetings between people who
安排人与人之间的会议
have different values for different
具有不同的价值
times in their calendar and who may not
他们日历中的时间，谁可能没有
tell you the truth about whether they're
告诉你他们是否是事实
available or not so for example they may
可用与否，例如，他们可能
lie to you and tell you I'm busy first
骗你，告诉你我先忙
thing in the morning just because they
早上的事情只是因为他们
don't actually want to come in first
其实不想先进入
thing in the morning and in principle
原则上在早上
it's fine that they they have a bad
他们有坏事很好
value for that time but it may be that
当时的价值，但可能是
turns out to be the only time that
原来是唯一一次
everybody else is available so it may be
其他人都有空，所以可能
better to be able to reward that person
更好地能够奖励那个人
strongly for coming in first thing in
强烈要求进入第一件事
the morning rather than not being able
早上而不是不能
to have the meeting at all so here what
完全开会，在这里呢
I want to do again now I have to do this
我想现在再做一次
in a setting where payments are possible
在可以付款的环境中
so I have to imagine either that I
所以我必须想像我
really am going to pay people bonuses
真的要给人花红
for coming to their meetings or I have
参加他们的会议，或者我有
to imagine that I have some kind of
想像一下我有某种
artificial currency which is still
仍然是人造货币
scarce which is used for meeting
用于会议的稀缺
scheduling and people care about so
日程安排和人们在乎
maybe you know in my case where somebody
也许你知道我的情况
has to come
必须来
in a really undesirable time for them
对他们来说真是一个不可取的时间
they accumulate a lot of credit that
他们积累了很多信誉，
they can use for something else that
他们可以用其他的东西
they value but again the way the VCG
他们很重视，但还是VCG的方式
mechanism would work here is it would
机制会在这里工作是
give everyone a dominant strategy for
给每个人一个主导策略
telling me all of the the values they
告诉我他们所有的价值观
have for the different times that which
在不同的时间有
meetings might happen and it will then
会议可能会发生，然后
come up with payments that make
拿出付款
everybody happy about having told me
每个人都高兴地告诉我
this and allow me to implement the
这并允许我实施
social welfare maximizing meeting
社会福利最大化会议
schedule so let's look at one more
安排时间，让我们再来看一个
example which indeed will work through
确实可以通过的例子
numerically in later videos in a
在后面的视频中以数字方式
stylized form this is the problem of
程式化的形式，这是问题
buying a path in a network and the
购买网络中的路径，然后
network I want to think about here is a
我想考虑的网络是一个
railroad network from the American
美国铁路网
Midwest in 1881 so each of these red
1881年在中西部，所以每个这些红色
lines here corresponds to a rail link
此处的线对应于铁路链接
that existed in this area in 1881 and I
在1881年我就在这个地区存在
don't know if this is actually true but
不知道这是否是真的，但是
I want to claim that each of these red
我想宣称这些红色
lines corresponds to a privately owned
行对应于私有
railroad that is owned by a different
拥有不同铁路的铁路
railroad operator certainly is the case
铁路运营商当然是这样
that in the early days of railroads in
在铁路的早期
the United States there were lots of
美国有很多
different privately owned railroads so I
不同的私有铁路，所以我
want to imagine that each of these
想想象每个
railroad links has its own private cost
铁路有自己的私人成本
for what it would cost to ship something
运送东西的成本
along the link over here is the Hocking
沿链接是霍金
Valley coal field which was an area of
山谷煤田是
coal production and of course over here
煤炭生产，当然在这里
is the city of Chicago and the problem
是芝加哥市和问题所在
that I'm interested in is the problem of
我感兴趣的是
shipping something shipping a bunch of
运送一些东西
coal from the Hocking Valley coal field
霍金谷煤田的煤
to Chicago so I as they the coal company
到芝加哥，所以我作为他们的煤炭公司
need to buy a sequence of links in the
需要购买一系列的链接
network that would get me all the way
网络让我一路走好
from the coal field to Chicago now if I
现在从煤田到芝加哥
was to use the VCG mechanism I could
我可以使用VCG机制
solve this problem by asking each of the
通过询问每个
coal companies what their utility is for
煤炭公司的效用是什么
being selected to ship coal and for each
被选择运送煤炭，每个
of them this would be a negative number
其中这将是一个负数
because it actually costs them something
因为这实际上使他们付出了一些代价
to do the shipping so each of them would
做运输，所以他们每个人都会
tell me a negative
告诉我负面
they would have a dominant strategy to
他们将拥有主导策略
tell me the truth about what their real
告诉我他们真实的真相
cost is I can then look at these numbers
成本是我可以查看这些数字
and the social welfare maximizing
社会福利最大化
outcome here is the shortest path in the
结果是这是最短的路径
network it's the the set of pads that
网络是一组垫
together get me from the Hawking Valley
一起带我离开霍金谷
coal field to Chicago and imposes the
煤田到芝加哥，并强加
least negative cost on all of the agents
所有代理商的最低负成本
now why would they be willing to be
现在为什么他们愿意成为
chosen if they're getting given if
选择他们是否得到如果
they're in a situation that may
他们处在一种可能
negatively value well to make this a
消极地重视，使其成为一个
dominant strategy VCG in this case is
在这种情况下，主导策略VCG为
going to end up paying all of the agents
最终要付给所有代理商
rather than I imposing payments on them
而不是我强加给他们
as it did for example in the
就像在
privatization example so in this example
私有化示例，因此在此示例中
it's going to figure out a way to pay
它将找出一种付款方式
the agents that makes them willing to
使他们愿意的代理商
have told me the truth and ends up
告诉我真相并结束了
buying the shortest path so overall what
购买最短路径总的来说是什么
if we see in here the VCG mechanism is
如果我们在这里看到VCG机制是
an amazing way of solving all of these
解决所有这些问题的惊人方法
apparently very different problems and
明显不同的问题，
indeed lots more and it again to remind
确实还有更多，再次提醒
you the property that it has is that it
你拥有的财产是
chooses the efficient or social welfare
选择有效或社会福利
maximizing outcome in a transferable
最大化可转让成果
utility setting in a way that gives
实用程序设置可以使
agents dominant strategies to tell the
代理商主导策略告诉
truth we'll spend the rest of this week
真相，我们将在本周余下的时间里度过
telling you in more formal detail how
更正式地告诉您
the BCG mechanism is defined how it
BCG机制的定义方式
works and what its strengths and
作品及其优势
weaknesses are
弱点是